<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
    <title>Hanley &amp; Co</title>
    <description>We are a family run Chartered Accountants practice with over 25 years experience.</description>
    <sections>
        <headerSection>
            <image>d+g.jpg</image>
            <title>Hanley &amp; Co</title>
            <subTitle>Chartered Accountants and Business Advisors</subTitle>
            <tagLine>Accountants You Can Talk To</tagLine>
        </headerSection>
        <section>
            <header>In a Nutshell</header>
            <content>
                <intro>Hanley &amp; Co is a family run practice with over 25 years experience as Practising Chartered Accountants.  We pride ourselves that we truly are 'Accountants You Can Talk To'.</intro>
                <paragraph>Our Partner Dean Logan and his friendly, qualified team are available to provide you with sound business and tax advice, and support throughout the year.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>We offer a free initial 'no obligation' consultation so you can talk through your requirements and and hear our advice, suggestions and an outline of services we can help you with.  Please phone us for an informal chat, send an email or just ring to arrange an appointment. We have offices in Ashton under Lyne, (covering Tameside and Greater Manchester) and Blackpool (covering Blackpool, Preston, Lytham, Kirkham, St Annes and the Fylde).</paragraph>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Services We Offer</header>
            <content>
                <intro>Naturally, we can take care of your paperwork – from dealing with the ‘Tax Man’, to looking after your bookkeeping, preparing your VAT returns and payroll, to finally preparing your annual accounts and your tax returns.</intro>
                <paragraph>If you're just starting out we can advise on the correct format of the business and if appropriate setup your limited company for a modest fee.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>We undertake proactive tax planning for every client. You can be sure your business and personal tax affairs have been carefully reviewed and any options for improvement explored and explained. We aim to minimise all clients tax liabilities and ensure clients understand what they need to pay and when.  No surprise tax bills!</paragraph>
                <paragraph>As Registered Auditors we can undertake any assurance engagements our larger clients may require.</paragraph>
                <subHeader>Bookkeeping</subHeader>
                <paragraph>If you would prefer to prepare your bookkeeping yourself we can recommend the right software for you to use, and be there to support you using it throughout the year. We can offer you expert advice with all Sage and Quickbooks systems and many others. We have a range of spreadsheet solutions to help you.  Naturally we deal with manual books and ledgers - as well.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>We are also offer clients access to a superb online bookkeeping system "KashFlow".  Nowadays this is the preferred choice for many of our clients.  Using the Kashflow system allows us to help you monitor your business throughout the year.  Kashflow will not just help you prepare your VAT returns and bank reconciliations, but also provides clear monthly reports.</paragraph>
                <video>https://www.youtube.com/embed/tFRhzOF-XA4</video>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Our Fees</header>
            <content>
                <intro>Our fees are competitive and based on the time 'actually' spent on your affairs. We prefer not to offer 'standard fixed fees' as we don't think you should pay for any service you don't choose to use.</intro>
                <paragraph>We think you, your business and your personal tax affairs are unique. When you engage us as your accountants we want to understand your individual requirements and we will estimate our fee according to the services you need.  We also offer a monthly standing order facility for you to pay towards our fees and we accept all major debit and credit cards.</paragraph>
                <quote>
                    <text>Probably my best decision over all my 30 years in business was to engage Hanley &amp; Co as my company accountants.</text>
                    <attribution>
                        <name>C Pimlot</name>
                        <company>A C P &amp; D Ltd</company>
                    </attribution>
                </quote>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Our Clients</header>
            <content>
                <intro>We are always interested in talking to new clients.  You may be an established business looking for alternative professional advice, a new business venture taking your first tentative steps or you may simply be looking for some help with your personal Self Assessment tax return.</intro>
                <paragraph>For over 25 years we have worked with a wide range of clients from small sole traders to individuals with rental property portfolios to multi-million pound turnover companies.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>You can rest assured that whatever your situation, we will probably have dealt with a similar business or individual previously. This enables us to help you and understand the real challenges and opportunities businesses like yours may experience.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>Over the years we have assisted a wide range of clients in many industries including many one person companies, IR35 companies, family businesses, tradesmen and subcontractors and small hotel and guest houses.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>Also we are one of the Country's leading advisors to Online Traders using eBay, Amazon etc - we have even published our own guide with specific advice for such businesses which is available for free.</paragraph>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Free Business and Tax Guides</header>
            <content>
                <paragraph>Our guides are easy to read and packed full of tips and relevant advice - whether you're setting up in business, looking to grow your existing business or simply want to ensure your tax liabilities (and hassle from HMRC) are as low as legally possible.</paragraph>
                <link>
                    <title>Email us to receive our guides</title>
                    <text>For details of our Kashflow online bookkeeping system, one of our free tax business and tax guides, please send us a quick email.</text>
                    <url>mailto:help@hanleyandco.co.uk</url>
                </link>
                <quote>
                    <text>Hanley &amp; Co give valuable and excellent advice on all money matters.  I trust them completely and would recommend them to anyone.</text>
                    <attribution>
                        <name>V Williams</name>
                        <company>P A S Medical Ltd</company>
                    </attribution>
                </quote>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>We'd Like to Meet You</header>
            <content>
                <intro>We are happy to meet you in or out of business hours, at your place of work, home or at our offices. Many new clients just start with a chat on the telephone. Just let us know what suits you and your schedule.</intro>
                <paragraph>Our free initial consultation allows us to introduce ourselves and to answer any questions you may have.  You'll be pleased to hear we do not speak 'accountants jargon'; just plain English.  We will provide you with a detailed report outlining our various recommendations for your business and a clear written fee estimate.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>If you already have an accountant please be assured our conversation will be totally confidential and if you do decide to work with us we will handle the simple changeover process for you.  If you decide not to proceed that's fine too; you're very welcome to use our initial advice and even receive our free monthly newsletters and free tax guides so we can keep in touch.</paragraph>
                <contact>
                    <telephone>0161 339 7502</telephone>
                    <telephone>01253 320018</telephone>
                    <telephone>01772 673377</telephone>
                    <email>help@hanleyandco.co.uk</email>
                    <openingHours>
                        <text>Monday to Friday, 9:00 - 17:00 (later appointments available)</text>
                        <schema>Mo-Fr 9:00-17:00</schema>
                    </openingHours>
                </contact>
            </content>
        </section>
    </sections>
</page>
