<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<page>
    <title>Hanley &amp; Co</title>
    <sections>
        <headerSection>
            <image>d+g.jpg</image>
            <title>Hanley &amp; Co</title>
            <subTitle>Chartered Accountants and Business Advisors</subTitle>
            <tagLine>Accountants You Can Talk To</tagLine>
        </headerSection>
        <section>
            <header>In a Nutshell</header>
            <content>
                <intro>Hanley &amp; Co is a family run practice with over 25 years experience as Practising Chartered Accountants.  We pride ourselves that we truly are 'Accountants You Can Talk To'.</intro>
                <paragraph>Our Partner Dean Logan and his friendly and qualified team are available all year round (not just once a year!) to provide you with sound business and tax planning advice and answer any queries you may have.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>We offer a free initial no obligation consultation so you can talk through your plans and situation and get our advice.  You can give us a call, send an email or pop in for a chat; we have offices in Ashton under Lyne and Blackpool and the Fylde.</paragraph>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Services We Offer</header>
            <content>
                <intro>Naturally we can take care of 'all the paperwork' on your behalf - from looking after your bookkeeping, VAT Returns and payroll, to finally preparing your annual accounts and your various tax returns.</intro>
                <paragraph>We also undertake proactive tax planning for every client as standard - so you can rest assured that your personal income tax, capital gains and even inheritance tax position is sound, as well as your business tax affairs.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>And if you're just starting out we can even form your company for you and deal with your statutory requirements.  And as Registered Auditors we can undertake any assurance engagements you require.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>If you would prefer to prepare your bookkeeping or payroll yourself we can recommend the right software for you, train you to use it and be there to support you using it throughout the year.  We are also very proud to offer you access to our very own online bookkeeping system free of charge.</paragraph>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Our Fees</header>
            <content>
                <intro>We prefer not to offer 'standard fixed fees' as we don't think you should pay for service you don't necessarily need.</intro>
                <paragraph>We think you and your business and personal tax affairs are unique so when you engage us as your accountants we want to take the time to understand your individual requirements and calculate our fee according to the bespoke service we will offer you.  We also offer the facility for you to pay towards our fees each month, so you aren't faced with a 'bill bill' once a year.</paragraph>
                <quote>
                    <text>Probably my best decision over all my 30 years in business was to engage Hanley &amp; Co as my company accountants.</text>
                    <attribution>
                        <name>C Pimlot</name>
                        <company>ACP &amp; D Ltd</company>
                    </attribution>
                </quote>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Our Clients</header>
            <content>
                <intro>We are always interested in talking to new clients.  You may be an established business looking for better advice and service from your existing accountant, a new business venture taking your first tentative steps or you may simply be looking for some help with your personal Self Assessment tax return.</intro>
                <paragraph>For over 25 years we have worked with a wide range of clients from window cleaners and taxi-drivers to individuals with significant rental property portfolios to multi-million pound turnover companies.  So you can be rest assured that whatever your situation, we will almost certainty have dealt with one or two like yours over the years so will be able to help with and understand the real challenges and opportunities businesses like yours experience.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>Over the years we have built up collections of clients in particular industries such as one man (or woman) consultants and contractor service companies (some IR35) and small hotel and guest houses.  Also we are one of the country's leading advisors to online and eBay traders - we have even published our own guide with specific advice available HERE.</paragraph>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>We'd Love to Meet You</header>
            <content>
                <intro>We are happy to meet you in or out of business hours, at your place of work, your home or at one of our offices.  Or we can even just have a chat on the telephone.  Just let us know what suits you and your schedule.</intro>
                <paragraph>Our free initial consultation allows us to introduce ourselves and to answer any questions you may have.  You'll be pleased to hear we do not speak 'accountants jargon'; just plain English.  We will provide you with a clear, written fee quotation together with a detailed report outlining our various recommendations.</paragraph>
                <paragraph>If you already have an accountant please be assured our meeting will be totally confidential and if you do decide to work with us we will handle the simple changeover process for you.  And if you decide not to proceed that's fine too; you're very welcome to use our advice and even receive our free monthly newsletters and free tax guides.</paragraph>
                <contact>
                    <telephone>0161-339-7502</telephone>
                    <email>help@hanleyandco.co.uk</email>
                    <openingHours>
                        <text>Monday to Friday, 9:00 - 17:00</text>
                        <schema>Mo-Fr 9:00-17:00</schema>
                    </openingHours>
                </contact>
                <quote>
                    <text>Hanley &amp; Co give valuable and excellent advice on all money matters.  I trust them completely and would recommend them to anyone.</text>
                    <attribution>
                        <name>V Williams</name>
                        <company>PAS Medical Ltd</company>
                    </attribution>
                </quote>
            </content>
        </section>
        <section>
            <header>Free Business and Tax Guides</header>
            <content>
                <paragraph>Our guides are easy to read and packed full of tips and relevant advice - whether you're setting up in business, looking to grow your existing business or simply want to ensure your tax liabilities (and hassle from the tax man) are as low as legally possible.</paragraph>
                <link>
                    <title>Link to our free business and tax guides</title>
                    <text>Download our free guides</text>
                    <url>http://hanleyandco.co.uk/tax-and-business/FreeGuides.php</url>
                </link>
            </content>
        </section>
    </sections>
</page>
